You see? These are too small.
你看到了吗? 这些太小了.
How big do you want them?
你想要多大的?
Twelve inches by eighteen inches.
12英寸×18英寸.
Twelve by eighteen. Fine.
12×18. 好的.
And not this thin material. It doesn't last.
还有,不要这种薄面料. 很不耐用.
I want thicker cloth.
我要厚一点的.
What about...
那...
And just plain white. No fancy designs.
只要素白色. 不要有花哨的图案.
OK.
And finished edges.
还有, 锁好边.
Would you like anything else?
你还要点别的吗?
Yes. I want a shipment of guest towels.
是的, 我还想要一批给客人用的毛巾.
200 towels.
200条.
Sixteen inches by thirty inches.
16英寸×30英寸.
100%cotton.
100%纯棉.
In "Warm Cream". With the hotel monogram.
"暖米色", 印上饭店的字母图案(monogram).
If you wish.
如果你想的话.
I do wish.
我确实想.
We have a new line of terrycloth robes.
我们还有一种新款毛巾浴衣(terrycloth robes).
They're lighter.
质地较轻.
Very nice for the hot weather.
非常适合热天用.
Can you send me a sample?
你能给我寄一件样品来吗?
Of course.
当然.
I'll decide then.
然后我再决定.
Always a pleasure doing business with you, NuLa.
和你做生意总是很愉快, NuLa.
Likewise, Vinny.
我也是, Vinny.
I'll call again in two weeks.
两周以后我再打电话.
See you then.
到时再见.
So long!
再见!
Good bye!
You always get the last word.
你总是说最后一句话.
Yes, I do.
是的.